<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vTank</title>
    <link>https://cloerner.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on vTank</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 08:22:30 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cloerner.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Running a Homelab in 2020</title>
      <link>https://cloerner.github.io/posts/running_a_homelab_in_2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 08:22:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloerner.github.io/posts/running_a_homelab_in_2020/</guid>
      <description>Why running a Homelab? You need time, you need money and you need electrical power. But where else can you test new software or new features? The cloud could be a good way. But clouds are often expensive, and I wanted to have my lab on-premises.
There are two ways to build a Homelab on your own. You can buy a big server and test the software in a nested kind of way, or you can buy two or more small form factor (SFF) servers to get the full &amp;ldquo;native&amp;rdquo; experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>64GB in an Intel NUC7i3</title>
      <link>https://cloerner.github.io/posts/64gb_intel_nuc7i3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 08:22:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloerner.github.io/posts/64gb_intel_nuc7i3/</guid>
      <description>Memory in the homelab. A topic that probably hits everyone. Most of the time CPU resources are sufficient, but memory is usually a bottleneck. My colleague William Lam has tested the new 32GB DIMMs in his Intel NUCs. Link
Unfortunately, William has no generation 7 NUCs. So I thought, take the 300 Euros and test it myself in my environment. I ordered the new DIMMs here.
The installation was super easy and after 10 minutes the new memory was installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABOUT</title>
      <link>https://cloerner.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 12:29:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloerner.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Christian Loerner. Welcome to my blog.
My carrier at VMware started in early 2016 as a Technical Account Manager in the PSO organization. Prior to that I worked as a senior consultant for several business parters here in Germany. At all I have over 16 years of IT experience. Especially in VMware of course! If you want to know what a TAM does, you can follow this link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why another blog about virtualization?</title>
      <link>https://cloerner.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 10:18:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloerner.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description> 2019&amp;hellip;time for another blog. Yes, I work for VMware. Therefore, there are many things that I try and test with our products. So far, I have written down all my experiences and ideas for myself, but I thought if it helps me, it will definitely help others. So I decided to start my own blog. Here it is.
Welcome to vTANK! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONTACT</title>
      <link>https://cloerner.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloerner.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description> Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>